Heat. Heat.
Hey. Hey. Hey.
Heat. Hey, Heat.
Heat. Heat. N.
Hey.
Heat.
Hey. Hey.
Heat. Heat.
Heat.
Heat. Hey, Heat. Hey. Hey. Hey.
coma.
Hello. Hello everyone.
I hope I am able.
Hello to all. Hello. Hello.
I hope I'm
so uh it's been a while I streamed the
show.
Uh stuff has been lately isogashi,
so I couldn't properly stream or do
stuff.
Yeah.
So yeah, today I thought of doing an uh
IRL stream. Today I thought of doing an
IRL stream so I can you know uh test out
all the features of the app I'm using
for streaming my U Mikasuki UA who's in
chat right now. Hello Urcha Kawa
and uh
yeah so many things. We'll just be
walking and just chatting. I guess I
have to re return back to my room in 1
hour. That's like 1000 p.m. for dinner.
Uh so
probably
I might do a I should not promise
anything but I can say that I may or may
not do a
um PC desktop stream after this today.
Uh I just wanted to play a little bit of
the P pop PO champions a little bit. So
yeah.
Okay, let's check out the camera thingy
and see how it's how it goes. I forgot
there's audio. I actually uh the new
feature. Let me introduce you to the new
features. There is now blur.
Before that, can you see this? Is it am
I audible?
Hey, one of the new features is this.
So one of the new features is this blur
mode. I can blur when the moment is uh
yay. I can blur people and everything.
So this is a new feature
uh uh a new addition and it's slider
type. So I can like now blur things.
Yeah. And one of the new things is that
we have zoom.
We have zoom. Earlier I used to manually
zoom. It was pain. But now I can zoom
into into places. Look at the house.
And uh there's exposure as well. I can
adjust the exposure if it's if it needs
lighting and stuff. I did ask Uchan to
like add more features. So I can add
more ISO stuff. ISO and other stuff.
How do you even reset a variable
position?
Wait, how do you reset this?
I can't I
Okay, I think I can just go take a walk
there day
maybe.
All right, I think I haven't gone this
way.
I'll just go this way then
go. Okay, let me read the chat.
Hello, Kalisa. Welcome, welcome. Joking
your shadow. Oh, I forgot. Wait, let me
turn on the blur again. [__] Uh, also
Kis, welcome. Also, did you know I saw
you chat on Nati Nati stream by the way?
I I was like, wait, I was watching
Nati's W and out of nowhere, I saw your
your username and I was like, wait, what
the I know this person. Wait, isn't is
this the same Camson I know? Uh, hey.
So, yeah, I was I was watching Nati's a
dual stream thingy and I saw you there
on a stream.
Yeah, I'll blur it a little bit.
Am I blurring my shadow?
Ah, shadow queen is
shadow queen is not blurry though. How
do I fix the shadow disappearing thingy?
How do I fix the shadow cone?
Hey,
bro. Sniping viewers now.
Stalker son Janai. Stalker Jai. I I was
uh Nati has the onscreen
um chat, right? The Danmar thingy bullet
chat. Uh so
yeah from that I uh I saw that oh yeah I
mean can you make can you help me make
for my live stream
help
Make it too much wind. Yeah. Give me the
power to text to speech. Not yet. I have
to ask ask him to help me do that.
What chat? Daku chat. Literally bullet
chat from Nikono. Whenever someone
comments it goes like a bullet train.
It pops up and goes away.
Talk. You have to breathe. I'm breathing
now.
There was a lady who was looking at me.
Yeah. Someone out of breath from
walking.
Is it creepy when it's blurred and
you're seeing this?
I don't know.
It's so windy today.
Today was like summer. It felt like
summer. It was so hot and then of
nowhere
it was in the evening it was windy and
today um at 5:00 p.m.
5:00 p.m. it became night time here
like after school classes became already
became nighttime like this vibe right
now this 900 p.m. 5. It was literally
that on from 5:00 p.m. onwards.
I think summer I mean winter season is
going to be like that. N
Yeah. Also uh continuing with the new
features of Vis uh Vispol Life which
will be rebranded uh soon I guess to a
different name. But yeah, so uh one more
things one one more thing I want to show
you guys is I can fetch
a direct stream. I thought that car is
going to hit me. Holy lord. Okay, one
more thing I want to say is I can fetch
the live
feed from my PC on my phone right now.
Do you want to see that? M again. Let me
set it up. M. Let me control my PC from
my phone. Uh, one second.
Wait, what the [__] Who's watching me?
What?
Oh my god. He Oh my god. Who?
What the is someone watching me?
Oh [__] bro.
Okay, so basically I can click on share.
Let me share my Oh my god, you added a
feature to share.
Share webcam, too. Holy lord, crazy
though.
Crazy. Crazy.
Um,
okay. So, uh, I'm going to connect it
right now. Uh, one second. My zero tier
is connected. So, I go to manifold, the
companion app. Tap to preview. Oh, wait,
wait, wait. I don't need to preview it.
I can put it in the Vispol life. Yeah,
yeah, yeah. Bro, I feel like Nati should
review I honestly feel like Nati should
review uh Ure's uh app he's he made.
Like this has so much potential, bro. I
want him to like see this.
I feel like I should Yeah, literally
what you're seeing right now is my
stream from my PC.
Isn't that so powerful, Dio? Like you
can literally see that from uh on my
phone. That's literally NDI and not NDI
but custom NDI over here. Local to local
even though I'm out of my house right
now. You can literally see the YouTube
my PC stuff. Crazy the show. And it goes
two ways. I can send my phone screen
to my PC. No need to use link to windows
or Sarah Sarafia thingy or scruppy or
any other stuff. So cool to show
where L holy I swear you never used to
say that before was
new update incoming with the new UI. Oh,
Ena.
Uh,
how crazy are you being able to see
everything on your phone to click it?
I've been skimming my eyes so damn hard.
No, I uh like just like uh you you have
watched Nati stream that time, right?
So, just like Nati is doing using uh
Apollo and Moonlight, same thing. I do
that on my phone too. Apollo and
Optimus.
Same thing. I do that.
Optimus and Moonlight. Yeah, same thing.
But I'm using OS Link. I only use uh
Moonlight for games like Box and stuff.
So,
and I can finally it doesn't crash
anymore when I all tap. all time as in
when I switch switch to a different app
and stuff. It's it's so wonderful that I
who remembers this area the factory
and the shiny road thingy.
Yeah.
So
the factory and the lighthouse. Do you
do you remember that stream I went
exploring uh like trying to go to
towards that live house area and I ended
up getting going somewhere so far away
and stuff
and and and I walked
uh 3 kilometers back home or something.
Yeah,
this is a restricted area.
Damn.
So nice.
Uh
it was so nice.
I have been spoiling this guy with a lot
of my abs. Yeah, you are. You have been
I Bro, I feel like I should show Nati
the power of this poor life. like I'm
waiting for you to like um I'm waiting
for you to like finish uh your um finish
your rebbranding for the app
uh for like next week or something
whenever you're done with that then I'll
just or I'll I'll ask you to send an
email to Ni then I'll vouch for I'll
watch for you like I'll I'll send him a
super chat of uh like a I'll send them a
donation thingy like to check out wish
for life or something or make a video
whatever like as long as it's fully um
when it's fully functional and
everything is I mean it is functional
I'm using it
so that like more features I'm begging
Aritan to like I'm begging Urchan to
like add the canvas no um ability to
draw on on screen thingy. So,
uh uh uh ability to draw on screen
thingy. So, that way I can draw thingy,
right? Imagine I can put my camera over
here. Then I uh switch to the canvas
mode can the draw mode and just draw an
arrow or something over there for people
who don't know what's happening like
annotating or something.
That would be so nice.
That would be so nice there.
Let me change my
thingy
to this.
Uh,
I'm watching Asen Gold right now on my
PC as you can see. Uh mate, as you can
see, I'm just watching Asmin Gold
on kick
playing like uh what is this game? Alen
ring. No, Dark Souls. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
I'll let that run in the background
while I take you with me.
So then
today, let's go.
Oh, it's just Nati and you both standing
on the peak of stream like honestly I
don't know like honestly this wouldn't
be possible without you who's on YouTube
channel right now but
if he didn't come to me saying like I
made a app what do you think about it
and ever since I started using it was
barebones okay it didn't have a camera
and everything I fell in love with it
because it's way better than I Pro,
Moblin, Linux, Broadcaster,
and everything
like it gets your basic streaming stuff
done. And the good thing uh the good
thing about it is doesn't use it doesn't
use like it doesn't use like camera as a
main thing. It uses um not like a canvas
like obvious canvas system.
What the
uh
Yeah,
Japan. It's Japan.
That's all.
Japo. Wait, let me get my blur on. Come
on.
I mean, do you want blur or do you don't
want blur? Should I just blur it when um
if it's bad if if it's a area I
shouldn't show on stream?
Uh
so
so yeah my in the future now I'm so I I
I don't know if I should say this but
you know how I streaming setup is so
expensive you have to do so much uh
subscriptions and etc all those stuff
now I'm begging Urchan to like actually
make
uh Viso live and his uh new newest
creation that's manifold thingy which I
showed earlier. I showed my PC, right?
Companion thingy. Yeah. So, I want him
to make it so I can connect external
camera and external mic
through a Raspberry Pi or an Orange Pi
and I can like um I can like give you
guys a better quality stream and better
audio stream.
on the on the go and everything will be
controlled from an Android phone. No
need of cloud OBS, no need of any other
stuff. You It's like NDI. You send uh
video feed from like my Raspberry Pi to
the phone thingy captures it. If my PC
was able to capture feed from like two 1
kilometer away, this guy
Yeah, I can do that. I can't speaking of
Japanese.
I don't know.
Yeah, I'm begging him. Get hardware
ready. I'll be on it. Let's go. I can't
believe you use kick. Yeah, I started
using kick. I'm I'm trying to level up
to 30 on kick. That's why I'm I'm
lurking on as goals like some 24x7
channels so I can like keep my laptop on
from morning till night every day and
far. I just want like that uh uh dark
uh blue no uh lavender color
um banner thingy. That's level 55.
No, level 50. So, I'm level 30 right
now. No, no. Ah, I'll be level 30.
So,
we ended up going to the lighthouse
area.
I kept on walking and walking and
that's whatever.
And I can like show you my screen. Let
me let me do the screen share thingy.
Let me see if I can do that without
sound
so I can't show you my uh actual screen
on stream right now. I haven't tested
this. It's first time. But yeah, let's
let's do that
screen. Can you see that?
Mimasa,
can you see it? Oh yeah, you can see it.
Oh my god.
Oh my god. You can you can see it. Wait,
how do I crop this?
I can't.
Yeah, you can you can see the UI and
everything. Uh Urchan will be upgrading
the UI. This whole stream became like
this uh thingy now.
Uh and I read my chat through here. Pro
chat to here. That's how I read it.
That's like toggles. That's like
sliders. There's dogs. Now browse. Uh, I
can see all the stuff. Cool. The show.
This became like a technical stream. Go.
But I'm excited. I'm so happy to show
you this.
So, you can also in the future test it
out. I'm a beta tester, so I wouldn't
want I want to test show this.
My shadow is here. Oh god.
I think I should done on blur. Maybe
that much blur should be good enough.
How's everyone doing?
Don't mind me. How are you guys doing?
How's life and everything?
Man, I'm so happy. Like I can like I can
like um do so much more now with the
manifold thingy.
Yeah,
it is so good, man. Honestly,
I am getting so much ideas in my brain
right now and I don't know what to do.
I suppose you're doing broke. Yes, I am
broke.
friend. Jesus loves you greatly. He has
many plans for you. Thank you, manly
womba.
Welcome to rich frame. Hello. Hello.
Good evening.
Uh also um not that uh
uh
I wanted to say like um
today
I bought
a CPU cooler
and uh uh I bought a CPU cooler and uh
what was it?
I bought a CPU cooler and a power supply
actually for my gaming uh streaming PC.
Um my streaming PC will arrive by the
end of this month probably. I did buy a
case and stuff.
Uh
uh
welcome to the stream
on uh please stay
but yeah uh
Wait,
we are buffering.
Wait, what about now? Tell me. I hope
I'm not buffering.
I have to check my stream. What the?
Not the Let me check my stream.
Come on.
Uh,
how do I check
if I'm live?
What the
It's so dark. Oh my god. I almost fell
down.
Oh, this is so dark though.
You must have Where am I even going
though, bro?
Bruh.
I'm live, right?
Hope I am.
Let me check the time.
9:27.
Oh, I am live. Okay, good. Good. But we
are buffering.
Hey,
why are we buffering this much?
Yeah, my mobile data is unstable.
Can't do much.
bad networks are. Uh, do you get
notifications when I make clips from
your Twitch? Uh,
I think Disco notifications runs
whenever you make a Twitch clip. It
automatically posts on Twitch and I'm
sorry, uh, on Discord. The Discord I
added,
it will do that apparently.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
So,
but yeah, I feel like honestly though um
I feel like one's visive
is polished. No, the only thing it
doesn't have right now is
uh network bonding.
But if that is there, I feel like more
more people will want to use it as a
good replacement for IL Pro and other
uh stream mobile streaming apps out
there.
That's the thing.
Uh
but yeah, manifold is does have if I'm
correct, manifold has network bonding.
Show
I also need to double test this network
bonding thingy.
I know where to buy like a
some
do you know those things these streamers
use like a router which has two SIM
cards or three SIM cards or four. It
kind of uses all four of them to give
you a good Wi-Fi thingy and it will
automatically switch in between those
four SIM cards. I want that stuff.
I made two.
Thank you for the respect and for the
chat. Hi.
Have a good one.
Uh
it's tapping into all the
Yeah.
But
it uses Wi-Fi
to
uh to it uses both internet Wi-Fi and
mobile data to
getated with Tra
is the Wi-Fi and the mobile data.
Make sure I always get
thousand messy
right now.
I'm in some like Oh,
really?
Okay.
I don't want to show
I don't want to show you my thing.
If I do show you my map, you I'll dox
myself. If I streamer, this wouldn't be.
But
yeah, so
Oh my god, I almost dropped the phone.
Oh god.
Go back to the buffering. Okay, fine.
Going to the factory. I have to walk 10
minutes.
Oh lord.
Yeah, this area does not have much
cellular network thingy. I can see my
rakutan sim uh signal is not strong.
Ah, I have to go back there.
Yeah. Bye
bye.
Yay.
What else we
show?
backpack and move around
like right door. Outdoor
But
big lines of code and brain brain
bursting stuff you have to do. I don't
know man.
Join
a show.
The network is crazy.
Is it not watchable?
Really?
But I'm going back home. I'm back home.
Going back to the factory.
Yeah, I'm going back to far today.
Buffering better now.
Please give me internet.
Internet hosy
internet.
Hello Relle. I'm doing good. How are you
doing? How's the pu pu puyo training arc
going for you? How's everything?
Hope it's going well.
Man, I miss war dogs. I want to get back
to war dogs when season 2 launches
on October 15th.
So, I'm waiting for that, honestly.
When season 2 comes out,
I'll instantly
play that.
Okay, this area has a cellular tower as
you can see on the top. The other areas
does not have like a cellula tower. This
is like a local farm in in Akia.
But there's like cool looking houses
though. Even though this place is really
big.
That's the crazy part.
Maya, what do you guys think? uh
about
so what do you think I should do to
improve these
I'm going to
one of the things is I'm using my phone
speaker cuz that's better quality than
my wireless mic
but in the future we'll have like a
dedicated mic wireless mic setup and
while and the
actual DSLR or
DSLR camera
like I'm I'm in the future I'll be
buying a vlogging camera
like a Sony camera or something which I
can use for desktop uh like desk uh top
down view of my desk on my uh PC streams
and also for IRL. I want a allin-one
camera in the future.
Not now though, but in the future. So,
I'm like thinking,
yeah, I should I should do something.
So, then
I feel like one of the things I need
right now is like a
better stabilization
for these streams like this.
So on it.
Yay.
God, it's so windy.
I have to walk all the way back, bro.
It's 20 minute walk.
Why did I come all the way here
for no reason?
It's always like that with me. end up I
I end up walking so much while I'm
streaming. I don't look at how much I'm
walking. I keep on walking, walking,
walking.
Uh
I bought a new cycle by the way. I mean,
I don't know if I told Yeah, my last I
stream I told you guys like
my cycle got stolen.
Uh I my the cycle I bought from my
school store that got stolen
recently.
It's been like 1 week now.
And I did file a police report and
stuff, but
they couldn't find it still.
Uh they couldn't find this child. So, I
have to like
um not that I have to like
I had to like buy a new one.
So, the
Oh, squishy camera.
Squishy. Uh
That lady just looked at me in the
cycle. I I didn't show you the the
people's face cuz that's uh insensitive.
Uh
yeah, but they were like,
"Why is this foreigner speaking so
loudly to his phone? What is he doing?
Is he on a call?" Little do they know
that I'm a YouTuber and I'm streaming.
Oh yeah. Bye.
Hello.
Last one wasn't found.
Put a GPS on this one. Wait, I cannot
put a GPS though. I mean, I could
technically I do have a that thing set
up,
that real time tracker thingy for IR IRL
streamers. I don't have it currently
turned on, but I did set it up back in
India when I used to do
those long drive streams
with my scooter.
That time we didn't have audio uh video
at the show.
Yeah.
Wow. Yeah. This is that place. Do you
remember?
Do you remember this place
that old stream or something? I used to
show this
uh
some things on the
Ah, my camera quality is so bad.
My camera quality is so bad. Oh god,
it's so windy. Look, it's everything is
windy.
Y everything is windy. Let me stand
still. You can see how strong the wind
is.
See that?
Oh god.
Bye.
I don't know where am I going. Yeah,
let's go back home before it's going to
be 10. Uh, the stream is going to be
strictly 1 hour or so.
But yeah, I can turn on blur.
Oh, do you want to see this or do you
want to want me to blur it?
Uh,
I can't blur it.
I can blur it a little bit like this.
Oh my god. How much did I walk?
Yeah. Bye.
How much did I walk today?
It is so good.
The outdoor streams are fun. Is it
really? Honestly, tell me the truth. I
know the the video of it is so pain. I
know cuz the camera is shaking cuz I'm
moving a lot. You have to think of it
like this. I'm having a power bank. I'm
holding a power bank with my phone and
with my right hand
my left hand is where I talk to you guys
and um yeah
show don't get born I talk. Hi. I want
I must
ah we have to walk so much far. We are
by
Oh, look at the ball.
The big ball is here.
The big ball.
I forgot this. This was here now.
I forgot about that. This was here. Ah,
the big ball.
Goodbye.
The big ball.
I forgot.
Some sometimes jock walks into horror
scenes.
I mean it's night time. I mean I want to
do morning streams but I have classes
and stuff. The only time I can do
morning streams is like
but none of you guys going to come there
on morning cuz time zone not. So, you
would have to watch the vault if you
want to experience morning streams.
But there's one thing you're going to
experience. That's going to be snow. I'm
going to touch my first reaction to
touching snow and feeling snow and like
making a small snowball and like uh
snowman and stuff. I'm going to do all
of that on stream,
bro.
I'm going to do that honestly though.
Oh yeah. For winter season,
I feel like I have to wear three or four
clothes cuz it's super cold and like, oh
no, you never touch snow. Nope. Never.
Ever. Ever. I have touched the budget
snow. That's your for your ice in your
free freezer and stuff, right? Shaved
ice and stuff. I've done that.
But
I never experience snowfall. Yeah. I
hope it's full snowfalls here in this
place. Or I'll just go to go Tokyo. I
don't care. I'll just go to Tokyo and
experience a snowfall.
Oh my god, it's it's shaking.
Yeah. But
yeah, but
how many years have you been? This is my
first year.
Yeah, I've been here for 6 months. This
uh wait, April, May, June, July, August,
September, October. Huh? This month will
be seventh month.
This month will be my seventh month.
Oh, look. Starbucks is there.
Do you want to see Starbucks or should I
just go back home? What do you guys want
to want me to do? Do you guys want to
see Starbucks again?
I'm not there.
There is Starbucks over there.
Starbucks. Those are trees so I can't
see it.
Starbucks is over there.
Show me some nature. Can you teach me
what network binding is?
I don't know.
I don't know. You tell me. Oh my god.
Bro, I just saw Bro, did you see that,
bro? Someone clip that. Someone clip
that. Someone clip that. Someone clip
that. Oh my god. Babe, did you see that?
Did you see that? That was Holo Alive.
Mo,
bro.
That was hol mio graffiti on the car.
Not uh not graffiti. That's the sticker
thingy. Oh my god. Bro,
bro.
Bro.
Oh my god.
Oh. Oh my god.
Oh,
crazy. I I think uh if anyone's clipping
that uh you can like uh click on if
you're on Twitch, there should be an
option to clip.
Um but yeah,
never clip. It's okay. It's okay. You
can uh you can go back like uh 1 minute
and clip it. I I think I can just know
the time. Uh 9:51, right? So, 9:50
p.m.
uh on screen. That's why there's a timer
on screen. Like clock on screen. Oh god,
it's so windy. That's why there's a
clock on screen. So, the seconds as
well. So, it helps me to like go back
and see what time uh I need to go back
and like look at some stuff I need to
fix or clip, etc., etc.
That's why I always prioritize having a
a stream clock with seconds.
Oh god, it's so windy.
Yeah. Bye. Windy now.
Yeah. Factory
is here.
Factory is here.
Wow,
the clouds are so nice. I wish I can
just sit down here. I wish they have a
chairman over here. Can just look at the
sky and like
ah
everything is so nice moment.
So
wait, I have an idea.
You added the option to share your
camera, right? On share your camera on
the PC client, right?
You remember what I told you?
Remember what I told you?
Should I do it a check?
Should I do that right now?
Wait, let me let me share
the
PC
camera webcam.
I want to see my what my roommate share.
Oh my god. It's the camera. Oh my god.
Oh my god. Okay, I did it. Okay, wait.
What the Oh god, this is so funny.
Where is a manifold?
Oh my god. I'm just going to do it.
Oh my god.
Well, I don't see it though.
It only shows display one.
M
wait. It's not showing though.
I want to see my camera.
Too dark. Oh, Roku. Hello. Welcome.
Welcome.
You made a clip. Oh, thank you. I'm
going on with this one. Wait. Let me
connect to my PC camera right now.
Like you guys can see this, right? my PC
right now. Wait, you can see my PC
streaming Asthma Gold, but no. Uh, yeah,
you can see my PC right now, but I want
to see if I can show uh if I can see the
camera.
Is my camera turned off?
I had to stop the display capture
display sharing, right?
Why is it not working?
I think my camera is off. What the? I
think my camera is off.
Wait,
wait, I can watch my own screen share
right on the PC client.
So, oh wait, I cannot.
So, there let me connect to the
uh thingy again.
It should be possible though.
No, it's not working.
I'm still connected to the
Okay, camera is not working, man. Boo
boo.
Wait, wait, wait, wait. Let me try a
different camera.
Let me try
NDI camera
and let's put a
display capture and let's put
uh like
let's put like
uh let's put like window capture too.
I'm sharing three network stuff. So that
would mean I can watch it, right? Okay.
This works. Uh, the Chrome browser shows
up. Display works, but webcam doesn't
work. I think you have to
fix that. I guess webcam doesn't is not
working apparently.
Go. The webcam coin is not working
apparently.
But yeah, display should be working.
Yeah, as you can see, display is
working. But um this play works. But
yeah, let's go sit down over there.
Okay.
Let me rechuten.
Yes, Rakuten.
Rakuten is good, but the issue is
is that a stray dog? Okay, it's their
dog. Okay. I was like, "Wait, can I
touch a dog? Will it bite me?" Then I
realized Oh, it's their dog.
Is it their dog?
Oh, yeah. They're walking the dog. Okay.
Okay. Let's go this way.
Uh, toggle from about.
Wait. Toggle from about.
Toggle from about. Wait, what?
Toggle from about.
What the
tole from about as in
about
offer cameras in the show? It is on.
What do you mean
that doesn't work though?
I did it. It's not working.
It's not working.
Jog shadow reveal part two. Oh, this
guy. Oh [__]
Okay. Blur. Okay. You can't make me make
out.
Taboom. I can't lie.
Ah, the Arcadia again.
Thank you Roku for renew becoming an
astral constellation. Thank you for the
thank you for renewing your membership
to me.
Thank you.
Hope you're doing well. I don't know if
you're still here, but thank you.
Where am I?
It's so dark.
This is literally a forest. Did you know
that?
Oh, yeah. Uh on Saturday, uh I from
apparently one of the student from my
part-time job, the morning one, he's
quitting. I got to see that moment when
I went to get my uh my cycle got stolen,
right? So when I bought my new one and I
I needed that pass school uh tag so I
can park it in my in the school my new
cycle. So um
my new cycle. So uh I saw the uh the
student who comes for the afternoon uh
uh shift cuz he got classes in the
morning and he was there wanting to quit
and I felt so bad. I know. Like in the
morning there's less work. In the
afternoon it's like really crazy
shitload of work and you get super
exhausted. It's so exhausting.
Uh and
yeah,
I have a weird feeling they'll ask me to
come in on Saturday. And of course I
want to do that, but um cuz I'm broke
right now. I need I need to somehow up
my uh hours of working.
So
more
I had uh
I have two part-time jobs. I really
don't want to work on Saturday and
Sunday, man. I can work how uh like I
can do my hardest on Monday to Friday. I
really don't want to work Saturday,
Sunday cuz those two days are my off
days I want for myself
to like relax and chill and stream.
Are you a student? I'm a language
student. I'm here to learn Japanese,
right? I'm I'm in here in Japan uh under
the student visa.
Oh, this light bulb is so good.
Can you even see it? Oh, you can't even
see it. Sorry.
There you go. Light bulb.
This automatic lights. It lights up when
you walk. Look at that. It detects I
think it's a heat sensor or something.
Heat sensor or like motion sensor.
It lights up.
Every Japanese household has it. Every
house has it. Every building has it.
Crazy technology.
You can't see that in India yet.
Oh, it's 1000 p.m.
Bro, I wanted to sneak up on my
roommate. What's he doing? I wanted to
like check the camera feed, but I can't.
Oh, boy. Wait, wait, come from this way,
right? Okay.
Wait, why are there students uh
on the street now?
ah club and
probably club
people who do athletic
stuff clubs.
God they wait it's 10 though
that light will be stol if I sell it
here.
So,
so Diana,
today was fun. I ended up showcasing the
new updates of the live streaming app
I'm using on my phone developed by
Mikasuki.
So, I I I did ask for a lot of new other
new features. I hope someday he do he uh
he he does have a hand
so I can like test it out and like show
you guys.
I think we can go this way. I want to go
that way but I will go this way.
And what the canvas I know the draw mode
give me draw mode then then what else?
um draw more than
uh does anyone from chat uh chat have
any ideas
like
already this app is so powerful
I'm asking for more things I'm making I
don't want to over do it but still I
want things which now people use
nowadays
yeah network bonding is something well
that can be worked later but uh can uh
the draw mode can be good helps a lot.
And there is scene transitions too.
Scene transition
for
Yeah, I think there scene time
transition time.
So
stalk them and eat them. Why? Why is
there a plastic bag here?
It's the waste bag.
I should have been loud cuz it's
everyone is sleeping at this time. Like
as you can see, some houses have lights.
Some are medias are closed shut.
Yeah, it's so quiet. I'm the only odd
one right now.
Yeah, boy.
I should blur
a little bit. Slight blur. Yeah, I think
one of the feature I would want cuz I'm
using toggle and sliders now.
Uh toggle is uh it's a fixed setup man.
Someone's using their wash machine for
laundry. Okay. Yeah, I could hear the
sound. Uh it's not person.
I have uh state A has blur on and 100%
and state B is blur off like visibility
is off.
Since uh state
A has broken 100% the sliders, it
doesn't work. Have to re turn them on
and like readjust.
Don't go can't lie.
Yeah, I think that will be fixed when
you add the bindings thingy for toggle,
right? So, I can customize it.
Do you know Chila's art? Yes, I know. I
have played a parasocial from Chila's
art
broh
should be smoother next up. Hi
paras.
There is a new game out there.
I forgot the name of it.
There is actually a new game out.
It's like
you're a
you're a VTuber.
No, it's like a I know I shouldn't say
this on stream, but do you remember the
lawsuit between a popular singer,
Japanese singer, and a YouTuber
and stuff,
which became a whole scandal and stuff.
That same thing
as a video game. you're a YouTuber and
you accidentally
you're dating a big uh idol
singer and stuff and out of nowhere
out of nowhere you get phoned out by
your fan creepy stalker fans
and
wait I can go here. Uh, you get fondered
by your creepy stalker fans and um
and then you the game literally am I
just ruining the plot? I don't know. And
and she comes out being like, "Yeah, I'm
the boyfriend of him this and that." You
you try not to let the drama tour take
all the views and cloud. You jump into
that thingy and grab everyone's
attention towards you kind of thingy and
then it's horror or something. I don't
know.
Not Oshino. I forgot the name.
I have book added it to my wish list on
my Steam.
I have to check the name out.
It's a really cool game apparently.
I want to play that.
If I can
show that around here. Oh yeah, this is
a new
uh recently constructed.
This this uh house is like a recently
constructed house and I think already
someone is uh living there.
Crazy.
It took them three months
running like at
11:00.
I see you back.
Buffering.
Why?
Wait, am I buffering right now?
Am
I buffering?
It is my issue.
It is my issue. Yeah, it is my issue.
Something. Okay.
I think it's my phone's uh routine and
mode thingy.
Do you want to see my cycle? A new cycle
I bought. [__] I'm I'm already
[__]
Okay.
Oh, show my
Oh, am I back?
Okay, I am back. Oh my god, what the
hell happened?
I'm so so sorry. I think my I think Z
single I think um
Sydney servers just died. So I'm back I
switched to
switched to Virginia server.
So apparently um Caster Labs couldn't
send the feed to Malt and because
Multimed Phil Field died uh everything
just shut down. I don't know what
happened. I know for a fact that it
happened the moment I was uh back in my
dometry. I have a Samsung
mode routine thingy on my phone. So when
I'm in the location, when I'm like uh 3
m or 1 m in this area, it automatically
turns on or connects to the Wi-Fi. So I
feel like because of that that messed up
the whole stream cuz it automatically
connected to the Wi-Fi, right?
Yeah. I feel I think you in order to fix
this issue, right? Even when it
automatically connects to a Wi-Fi or a
network change thingy, I feel like you
can fix it if you do implement the bond
network bonding thingy.
If you can implement the network bonding
thing, I feel like that can fix it cuz
even if there's if it connects to a
Wi-Fi uh or something some other Wi-Fi,
it'll still keep on keep it will not
affect the stream.
I don't know what to say.
I just hope I'm live right now.
Also, there's an aeroplane in the sky.
In the far in the sky, in the clouds,
like I I saw like stuff.
But yeah, as sad as as it is, guys, uh
it's 10:30. It's going to be 10:30. So,
I'll wrapping I'll be wrapping up the
stream over here.
So,
uh before I end stream, I want to double
check
Oh, my thingy.
M. Just give me a minute. Just want to
check if I'm still live. I am live,
right? 1021.
Am I live, brother? Oh my god, it's so
laggy.
Uh, okay. I'm live. Okay, I'm live.
Okay, why is the YouTube like stuck?
Stuck.
I wanted to show you the cycle. I think
it disconnected when I was showing you
the cycle. Um, sorry. Uh, but
but it is what it is. If you want like a
picture of it, I think I can like show a
picture.
That's not a big deal.
I think I have some picture of it.
My new cycle looks like this. By the
way, I can like just show this. I guess
looks like this. It's a really good
cycle. Uh I I feel like I'm in a Land
Rover or like a big You know that
feeling when you buy a big heavy SUV or
something with big tires or something? I
feel like that whenever I'm riding this.
It has those big tires as you can see.
It's super good.
Well, I wanted to show you that. But
yeah, in end stream died
technical issues came the moment I
reached
home. Wow. Well, it's fine. It's okay.
It's good. But yeah, it's 10:30. Thank
you for sticking around and thank you
for watching everyone. I will wrap it up
over here. It's 1 hour 35 minutes.
Hi. I was supposed to wrap up the 5
minutes before, but yeah. Thank you
everyone for coming.
I'll go eat my dinner and go sleep. Or
if possible, I'll do a second stream,
desktop stream, just playing Puyo Puyo
for a bit. Or maybe not. I'll just watch
anime. There's so many new animes. So,
I'll just watch animes and stuff and
like sleep. Tomorrow, we'll do Puyo Puyo
desktop stream then. Yeah, we'll do
that. Hi.
So, Raja, thank you all for coming by.
I'm sorry my internet died earlier. Uh,
it was a network thingy. It connected to
my Wi-Fi and that ruined everything. Um,
so yeah. So, yeah. Thank you again. And
again, if you have missed it, this was
the cycle I bought. That's this was what
what I was trying to show you guys, but
it died.
But yeah, thank you again. Thank you.
All the people who came by today are
Thank you again for coming by. I'm still
here. Then Callie, thank you for coming
by.
Uh then Wilder. Oh my god, Wilden was
here.
I didn't see him. [__]
Thank you, Wilden. And Epipan,
thank you for coming by.
And then uh
Manly Bombas, thank you for coming by.
You're new here. Welcome to the
Conellers
concert plates. Uh then
then then Rishaan came by today. Thank
you for coming by. And Konadasan came by
today. And uh Roku, thank you for coming
by and thank you for the uh becoming a
member on YouTube, becoming ashual
constellation on YouTube. Thank you.
Then um
yeah, then I got reconnected and Kadasan
and Hurang came by. So that's everyone.
Thank you to all the lurkers who came by
today. Thank you so much. I hope you had
enjoyed the stream. It was me showing uh
new uh additions and new features to the
streaming uh app I'm using and all the
ideas I show um like talked on stream
like and stuff. And we ended up
exploring that uh light light tower
thingy again. Uh but yeah, I dreams are
fun. I just wish I can improve it little
by little over time. But yeah, so far
this is so good. No, I'm so happy I can
show you my desktop. I can screen even
if I'm streaming on uh uh desktop like
on PC OBS, I can show you my camera feed
without any external plugins. Like I can
this has like a two-way support. a lot
of good things. I'm so thankful to
Mikasuki U for making so many updates
and stuff. Mo poor poor baka he uh like
stayed day and night to like code all of
this like crazy though. But yeah, thank
you so much for making this happen.
Yeah, but yeah, thank you. Can't wait
for the future uh features you'll add
because of me.
But thank you again.
Have a good one. Have a good night. And
bye-bye.
I'll see you guys in the next stream.
Okay. Hi, M.
Bye-bye.